https://www.spartan.edu/privacy-notice-california-residents/

COVID-19 Information:  Spartan College is enrolling and continuing to support students in their educational goals during COVID-19
Who We Are
Established in 1928, Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology has trained over 100,000 pilots and technicians. We have campuses located in the following areas: Tulsa, OK; Los Angeles, CA; Inland Empire, CA; and Denver, CO. Spartan students have come from across the United States and over 62 countries.
About Us
Why Choose Spartan College?
Spartan College has been training professionals for aviation and related industries. We provide a supportive educational environment that encourages active participation in learning while providing quality career-oriented education programs.
Why Choose Spartan
Our History
Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology was founded in Tulsa, Oklahoma as Spartan School of Aeronautics by W.G. Skelly, President of Skelly Oil Company, on September 27, 1928. He established Spartan Aircraft Company and formed the corporation which built Tulsa Municipal Airport (now called Tulsa International Airport).
Our History
Mission, Purpose, and Values
The mission of Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology is to provide career-oriented diploma and degree programs in aviation and technology. We impact generations by providing knowledge and skill to students from across the street and around the world. We value innovation, respect, integrity, safety, and excellence.
Our Mission
Accreditation
Accreditation is important because it helps determine if an educational institution meets or exceeds the minimum quality standards set by the accrediting body. Accreditation can help you determine whether a college is in good standing, and it helps employers better understand the caliber of education you received.
Our Accreditation
Jobs at Spartan
Curious about the next chapter in your life? Consider a career at Spartan College.
Learn More About Spartan Jobs
Programs
Aviation Maintenance Technology (Oklahoma & Colorado)
Aviation Maintenance Technology / Airframe & Powerplant (California)
Aviation Electronics Technology
Aviation Flight
Nondestructive Testing Technology & Quality Control Management
Bachelor's in Technology Management
Locations
Tulsa Area
Denver Area
Los Angeles Area
Inland Empire Area
Admissions
Admission Overview
Scholarships
Financial Aid
Military Students
International Students
Admission Overview
We are excited that you are considering Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology! Many of our incoming students are excited to begin their education, but careful research should be done to be sure you know what to expect.
Find Out More
Scholarships
Looking for a scholarship to help pay for school? Contact Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology today for more information on scholarship opportunities! Scholarships may be available to those who qualify.
More About Scholarships
Financial Aid
Investing in your education is investing in your future. We understand the stress associated with paying for college and for that reason our Financial Aid Team does their best to make our students aware of all the financing options available for qualified students.
Learn More About Financial Aid
Military Students
At Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology, we are proud of our military heritage. Since 1928, we have been providing training for members of the armed services- active duty, reserves, veterans, and their dependents.
Learn More on Military Students
International Students
If you are an international student, we encourage you to take advantage of services designed to help you achieve your educational goals. Whether you are deciding on one of Spartan’s aviation degree/diploma programs, need assistance with your immigration papers or have questions about where to find your first class, the Spartan Office of International Student Services is here to help.
Learn More on International Students
Students
Student Services
Student Resources
Career Services
Career Fairs
Online Student Orientation
Spartan Gear
Student Services
At Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology, we care deeply about the success of our students. This is why we provide them with a variety of support services.
Our Student Services
Student Resources
At Spartan College, we care deeply about your success.
This is why we provide a variety of support services to help you overcome challenges that can stand in the way of your success. We are here to help by providing assistance with transportation, housing,
food, or other types of support services.
Our Student Resources
Career Services
A service we afford students at Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology is assisting them beyond graduation. Through continual contact with industry-related companies and business leaders, our Career Services department is able to cultivate employment opportunities.
Our Career Services
Career Fairs
Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology prides itself on building and maintaining relationships with local and national employers. We help our students and graduates with a variety of needs such as resume preparation, cover letter writing, and interview guidance.
Our Career Fairs
Online Student Orientation
If you are an international student, we encourage you to take advantage of services designed to help you achieve your educational goals. Whether you are deciding on one of Spartan’s aviation degree/diploma programs, need assistance with your immigration papers or have questions about where to find your first class, the Spartan Office of International Student Services is here to help.
Our Online Student Orientation
Spartan Gear
Looking for Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology apparel?
Look no further, as our Spartan Gear website offers many options to look your best!
Spartan Gear Store
Alumni
Alumni
Testimonials
Transcript Request
Alumni
Spartan alumni are as diverse as the aerospace industry itself. Now that you’re ready to make your mark in the world, you can use the Spartan Alumni page as a great resource for accessing your academic records, maintaining your contact information, and keeping in touch with other graduates and Spartan College staff.
Our Alumni
Testimonials
Wondering what it’s like to train at Spartan College? Find out from the source – our graduates! Pick a location and find out more.
Tulsa Area
Denver Area
Transcript Request
Due to federal privacy laws, academic transcripts cannot be released without a signed Spartan College Transcript Request Form. Forms may be submitted to the Office of the Registrar via U.S. Mail, delivery service, in-person, or email (address found in the forms below), and the $5.00 transcript request fee must be paid prior to the release of transcripts.
Learn About Transcript Requests
Contact
Contact Us
Request Information
Schedule a Tour
Contact Us
No matter where your interest lies, at Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology, we have five locations, offering a variety of programs tailored to meet your needs.
Contact Us
Request Information
If you would like to learn more about Spartan College and our program offerings, fill out the form below to request information, and we will have one of our admissions representatives contact you!
Request More Info
Schedule a Tour
Thank you for your interest in Spartan College of Aeronautics and Technology. We would love to show you around! Please fill out the form below so we can tailor your tour to your area of interest.
Typically, campus tours are available during business hours, Monday through Friday, excluding holidays.
Schedule a Tour
About
About Spartan
Why Choose Spartan
History
Mission and Goals
Accreditation
Jobs At Spartan
Spartan News
Programs
Aviation Maintenance Technology (Oklahoma and Colorado)
Aviation Maintenance Technology (California)
Aviation Electronics Technology
Aviation Flight
Nondestructive Testing Technology
Quality Control Management
Bachelor’s in Technology Management
Locations
Tulsa Campus Area
Denver Campus Area
Programs
Aviation Maintenance Technology (Oklahoma and Colorado)
Aviation Maintenance Technology (California)
Aviation Electronics Technology
Aviation Flight
Nondestructive Testing Technology
Quality Control Management
Bachelor’s in Technology Management
Locations
Tulsa Campus Area
Denver Campus Area
Home » Privacy Notice For California Residents
This Privacy Notice for California Residents applies solely to the personal data of individuals who reside in the State of California (“consumers” or “you”) and forms a part of and supplements the information contained in our Privacy Policy. We have provided this Privacy Notice for California Residents to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the “CCPA”) and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this notice.Your Rights and Choices: The CCPA provides consumers with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your CCPA rights and how you may exercise those rights.Access to Specific Information; Data Portability Rights. You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you: (a) the categories of personal information we collected about you; (b) the categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you; (c) our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information; (d) the categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information, if any; (e) the specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request); (f) if we disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained. Please note that we do not sell personal information.Deletion Request Rights. You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers, if any, to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies. We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) to: (a) complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you; (b) detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities; (c) debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality; (d) exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law; (e) comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et. seq.); (f) engage in public or peer-reviewed research in accordance with Section 1798.105 (d)(6) of the CCPA; (g) enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us; (h) comply with a legal obligation; or (i) make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.Exercising Your Rights. To exercise the access, data portability and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either visiting https://www.spartan.edu/contact-us/ or emailing privacy@spartan.edu.Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information.You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within any 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must: (a) provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify that you are the individual about whom we collected personal information or that you are an authorized representative of that individual; and (b) describe your request with sufficient detail to allows us to properly understand, evaluate and respond to it. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to you. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.Response Timing and Format. We endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of the verifiable consumer request. The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance. We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.Non-Discrimination. We will not discriminate against you for exercising your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not: (a) deny you goods or services; (b) charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties; (c) provide you a different level or quality of goods or services; (d) suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services. However, we may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA that can result in different prices, rates or quality levels. Any CCPA-permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information’s value and contain written terms that describe the program’s material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt in consent, which you may revoke at any time.Contact Information: If you have any questions or comments about this notice, the ways in which we collect and use your information described in this notice, your choices and rights regarding such use or wish to exercise your rights under California law, please do not hesitate to contact us at:Website: https://www.spartan.edu/contact-us/Email: privacy@spartan.edu
Programs
Aviation Maintenance Technology (OK & CO)Aviation Maintenance Technology / Airframe & Powerplant (CA)Aviation Electronics TechnologyNondestructive Testing Technology & Quality Control ManagementAviation FlightBachelor’s In Technology Management
Locations
Tulsa Area
Denver Area
Los Angeles Area
Inland Empire Area
Consumer Information
Tulsa AreaDenver AreaLos Angeles AreaInland Empire AreaCoronavirus (Covid-19)
Contact
Admissions and Program Info:918.831.8688If International:1.918.836.6886
Affiliate Partner Program | Privacy Policy | Opt-out Policy | Privacy Notice – California Residents
© 2020 SPARTAN COLLEGE OF AERONAUTICS AND TECHNOLOGY. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
